<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Halo</string>
    <string name="title_learn">Learn</string>
    <string name="title_prevent">Prevention</string>
    <string name="title_report">Report</string>
    <string name="title">What is child trafficking and sexual exploitation?</string>
    <string name="child">Child trafficking and sexual assault are deeply distressing issues that continue to plague societies worldwide. They not only violate the rights of innocent children but also inflict long-lasting physical, emotional, and psychological harm. Here are some key points to consider regarding these grave concerns:</string>
    <string name="child2">- Child trafficking involves the illegal recruitment, transportation, and exploitation of children for various purposes, including forced labor, sex trafficking, and organ trafficking.
\n\n
- It is a highly profitable criminal industry, driven by factors such as poverty, conflict, and social vulnerability, which makes children more susceptible to manipulation and coercion.
\n\n
- Traffickers often deceive families with false promises of better opportunities for their children, only to subject them to horrendous conditions, physical abuse, and sexual exploitation.
\n\n
- The consequences of child trafficking are devastating, with victims suffering from physical injuries, psychological trauma, disrupted education, and a loss of trust in society.
</string>
    <string name="sa">- Sexual assault against children is a severe form of abuse that involves any sexual act or behavior inflicted upon a child without their consent.
\n\n
- The perpetrators of sexual assault can be strangers, acquaintances, or even family members, which makes it a complex and challenging issue to address.
\n\n
- Victims of sexual assault endure profound emotional and psychological trauma, including feelings of shame, guilt, fear, and a distorted sense of self-worth.
\n\n
- The long-term effects of sexual assault can manifest as post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD), depression, anxiety, self-harm, substance abuse, and difficulties in forming healthy relationships.
</string>
    <string name="conc">It is crucial to raise awareness, strengthen legal frameworks, and provide comprehensive support services for survivors to combat child trafficking and sexual assault effectively. The protection and well-being of children must be a priority for individuals, communities, and governments, working collectively to create a safe and nurturing environment for every child.
\n\n\n\n Heres a look at what sexual exploitation looks like:
        \n\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="desc_prevent">How can you prevent child trafficking and sexual exploitation?</string>
    <string name="tip_1">Raise awareness: Educate yourself and others about the realities and dangers of child trafficking and sexual exploitation. Share information through social media, community events, and workshops to help raise awareness. \n \n</string>
    <string name="tip_2">Promote child protection: Encourage the implementation of child protection policies in schools, community organizations, and other institutions. These policies should include strict background checks for employees and volunteers who work with children \n\n.</string>
    <string name="tip_3">Report suspicious activities: If you suspect child trafficking or sexual exploitation, report it to the appropriate authorities immediately. In many countries, there are helplines and hotlines dedicated to reporting such cases. \n\n</string>
</resources>